{
    "subject": "resource/Bob_Bender",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Robert Michael \"Bob\" Bender (born April 28, 1957) is an American professional basketball coach, currently working as an assistant with the Milwaukee Bucks of the National Basketball Association (NBA). Born in Quantico, Virginia, He attended Bloomington High School in Bloomington, IL, where he was an All-American in basketball. Bender has the distinction of being the only individual to play on two different teams in two different NCAA Championship games. He was a freshman on Bob Knight's undefeated 1976 Indiana team and played point guard at Duke from 1977\u201380, including an appearance in the title game against Kentucky. Bender was drafted by the San Diego Clippers in the sixth round before his senior year, but did not play.He began his coaching career as an assistant at Duke under Mike Krzyzewski. He later served as head coach at Illinois State University and the University of Washington, and was an assistant with the Philadelphia 76ers.Bender is married to his wife, Alice, with whom he has two children: Mary Elizabeth and Robert Michael Bender III.On June 17, 2013, Bender was hired as an assistant coach of the Milwaukee Bucks, under Larry Drew, of whom he was an assistant to at the Atlanta Hawks.",
    "human_readable": "Bob Bender's abstract is Robert Michael 'Bob' Bender (born April 28, 1957) is an American professional basketball coach, currently working as an assistant with the Milwaukee Bucks of the National Basketball Association (NBA). Born in Quantico, Virginia, He attended Bloomington High School in Bloomington, IL, where he was an All-American in basketball. Bob Bender has the distinction of being the only individual to play on two different teams in two different NCAA Championship games. He was a freshman on Bob Knight's undefeated 1976 Indiana team and played point guard at Duke from 1977\u201380, including an appearance in the title game against Kentucky. Bob Bender was drafted by the San Diego Clippers in the sixth round before his senior year, but did not play. He began his coaching career as an assistant at Duke under Mike Krzyzewski. He later served as head coach at Illinois State University and the University of Washington, and was an assistant with the Philadelphia 76ers. Bob Bender is married to his wife, Alice, with whom he has two children: Mary Elizabeth and Robert Michael Bender III. On June 17, 2013, Bob Bender was hired as an assistant coach of the Milwaukee Bucks, under Larry Drew, of whom he was an assistant to at the Atlanta Hawks.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8372715711593628,
            "question": "Who was Bob Bender's coach at Duke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8287914991378784,
            "question": "What year was Bob Bender born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8154371380805969,
            "question": "Name two universities where Bob Bender served as head coach."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8088581562042236,
            "question": "Which university did Bob Bender play basketball for before Duke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.807880699634552,
            "question": "Where did Bob Bender attend high school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8077513575553894,
            "question": "Under whom was Bob Bender an assistant coach at the Atlanta Hawks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.801460862159729,
            "question": "What team drafted Bob Bender before his senior year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7846147418022156,
            "question": "What position did Bob Bender play in college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7702746987342834,
            "question": "What team did Bob Bender join in June 2013?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7610876560211182,
            "question": "Who is Bob Bender's wife?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bob Bender's abstract is Robert Michael 'Bob' Bender (born April 28, 1957) is an American professional basketball coach, currently working as an assistant with the Milwaukee Bucks of the National Basketball Association (NBA). Born in Quantico, Virginia, He attended Bloomington High School in Bloomington, IL, where he was an All-American in basketball. Bob Bender has the distinction of being the only individual to play on two different teams in two different NCAA Championship games. He was a freshman on Bob Knight's undefeated 1976 Indiana team and played point guard at Duke from 1977\u201380, including an appearance in the title game against Kentucky. Bob Bender was drafted by the San Diego Clippers in the sixth round before his senior year, but did not play. He began his coaching career as an assistant at Duke under Mike Krzyzewski. He later served as head coach at Illinois State University and the University of Washington, and was an assistant with the Philadelphia 76ers. Bob Bender is married to his wife, Alice, with whom he has two children: Mary Elizabeth and Robert Michael Bender III. On June 17, 2013, Bob Bender was hired as an assistant coach of the Milwaukee Bucks, under Larry Drew, of whom he was an assistant to at the Atlanta Hawks.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6252_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What team did Bob Bender join in June 2013?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6252_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position did Bob Bender play in college?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6252_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What team drafted Bob Bender before his senior year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6252_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6252_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about Bob Bender's coaching career as an assistant and head coach for various teams, including Duke, Illinois State University, the University of Washington, the Philadelphia 76ers, the Atlanta Hawks, and the Milwaukee Bucks. The information also mentions his playing career at Indiana and Duke, and his distinction as being the only individual to play on two different teams in two different NCAA Championship games."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided information about Bob Bender in the documents supports the given abstract. The documents include details such as his full name (Robert Michael 'Bob' Bender), birth date (April 28, 1957), coaching career, basketball playing experience, and his current position as an assistant coach with the Milwaukee Bucks of the NBA."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}